歌手：Ylvis
压制:随Feng
The Fox
狐狸
Dog goes woof Cat goes meow
狗会汪汪 猫会喵
Bird goes tweet and mouse goes squeek
鸟会鸣叫 老鼠吱吱叫
Cow goes moo Frog goes croak
牛会哞 青蛙会呱呱叫
and the elephant goes toot
大象会嘟嘟
Ducks say quack and fish go blub
鸭子呱呱 鱼咕噜
and the seal goes ow ow ow
海豹嗷嗷嗷
But there's one sound
但是有一种声音
That no one knows
没有人知道
What does the fox say?
狐狸怎么叫
Ring-ding-ding-ding-dingeringedding!
Ring-ding-ding-ding-dingeringedding
gering-ding-ding-ding-dingeringeding!
gering-ding-ding-ding-dingeringeding
What does the fox say?
狐狸怎么叫
Wa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pow!
Wa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pow
What does the fox say?
狐狸怎么叫
Hatee-hatee-hatee-ho!
Hatee-hatee-hatee-ho
What does the fox say?
狐狸怎么叫
Joff-tchoff-tchoffo-tchoffo-tchoff!
Tchoff-tchoff-tchoffo-tchoffo-tchoff!
Tchoff-tchoff-tchoffo-tchoffo-tchoff
Joff-tchoff-tchoffo-tchoffo-tchoff!
Joff-tchoff-tchoffo-tchoffo-tchoff
What does the fox say?
狐狸怎么叫
Big blue eyes Pointy nose
蓝色的大眼睛 尖尖的鼻子
Chasing mice and digging holes
追逐老鼠和挖洞
Tiny paws Up the hill
尖着脚尖溜上山坡
Suddenly you're standing still
突然 你站着不动
Your fur is red So beautiful
你的毛皮是红色的 如此美丽
Like an angel in disguise
像一个伪装的天使
But if you meet a friendly horse
但如果你遇见一匹友好的马
Will you communicate by
你会用这沟通
mo-o-o-o-orse? mo-o-o-o-orse? mo-o-o-o-orse?
mo-o-o-o-orse? mo-o-o-o-orse? mo-o-o-o-orse
How will you speak to that
你会怎么叫
ho-o-o-o-orse? ho-o-o-o-orse? ho-o-o-o-orse?
ho-o-o-o-orse? ho-o-o-o-orse? ho-o-o-o-orse
what does the fox say?
狐狸怎么叫
Jacha-chacha-chacha-chow!
Jacha-chacha-chacha-chow
Chacha-chacha-chacha-chow!
Chacha-chacha-chacha-chow
What does the fox say?
狐狸怎么叫
Fraka-kaka-kaka-kaka-kow!
Fraka-kaka-kaka-kaka-kow
What does the fox say?
狐狸怎么叫
A-hee-ahee ha-hee!
What does the fox say?
狐狸怎么叫
A-oo-oo-oo-ooo! Woo-oo-oo-ooo!
What does the fox say?
狐狸怎么叫
The secret of the fox Ancient mystery
狐狸古老神秘的秘密
Somewhere deep in the woods
在那树林的深处
I know you're hiding
我知道你隐藏着
what is your sound?
你的声音是什么
Will we ever know?
我们会知道吗
Will always be a mystery
将永远成为一个谜
What do you say?
你会怎么叫
You're my guardian angel
你是我的守护天使
hiding in the woods
躲藏在树林里
what is your sound?
你的声音是什么
Will we ever know?
我们会知道吗
I want to I want to I want to know
我想要 我想要 我想要知道...
压制:随Feng